{
    "id": "633a3123016d4fc7b6597aae3e56c3b1",
    "title": "Adjectives Worksheet",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He went to the shop to buy a new coat for himself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "shop",
                "new"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was an honest man.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "honest",
                "man"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "They took active part in all the ceremonies.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "active",
                "part"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Students and parents are invited to the inaugural function.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "invited",
                "inaugural"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "This shop sells bronze and wooden articles.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shop",
                "wooden",
                "articles"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She was in a cheerful mood.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "she",
                "cheerful",
                "mood"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We live among respectable people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "live",
                "among",
                "respectable"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was nice to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "nice",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We learnt a terrible thing today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "learnt",
                "terrible",
                "today"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The sun in our solar system will eventually become a red giant.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "solar",
                "system",
                "giant"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Kabir wrote couplets and short poems.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wrote",
                "couplets",
                "short"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The camelâ€™s back was puffing up into a great big curved hump.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "puffing",
                "great"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}